<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>The Signal - Yahoo! News</title>
<link>http://news.yahoo.com/rss-signal/</link>
<description/>
<language>en-US</language>
<copyright>Copyright (c) 2012 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved</copyright>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 10:19:07 -0400</pubDate>
<ttl>5</ttl>
<image>
<title>The Signal - Yahoo! News</title>
<link>http://news.yahoo.com/rss-signal/</link>
<url>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/us/nws/th/main_142c.gif</url>
</image>
<item><title>Can Republicans take the Senate? The odds are in their favor</title><description>With the unrelenting focus on every aspect of the fight for the White House, it's easy to forget that the Senate is also up for grabs on Election Day. In fact, it could be the presidential election that determines the upper body's control: If the Republicans win a net total of three seats, the Senate [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/republicans-senate-odds-favor-141907645.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 10:19:07 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/republicans-senate-odds-favor-141907645</guid></item><item><title>Gambling on war: The dark side of prediction markets</title><description>Over and over, we've found that the political prediction markets offer accurate, real-time information on the odds of a politician's victory in any major contest. But there's a darker, less tested corner to some of the sites that allow people to wager real money on the outcome of world events. The gambling site Intrade, for [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/gambling-war-dark-side-prediction-markets-145801040.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 10:58:01 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/gambling-war-dark-side-prediction-markets-145801040</guid></item><item><title>Save the American Community Survey!</title><description>When the U.S. Constitution became law in 1789, it made sense for the government to take a survey of its citizens only once a decade. The agrarian economy meant the population largely stayed put and grew at a much slower pace than it does today.</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/save-the-american-community-survey.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 13:33:46 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/save-the-american-community-survey</guid></item><item><title>The rational case for why Obama supported gay marriage when he did</title><description>When Barack Obama announced his support for gay marriage on May 9, most commentators immediately turned to how this would affect his chances in the 2012 campaign. Now that a few days have elapsed, we can say with confidence that the effect was negligible. The following chart illustrates the most accurate and real-time forecasts, derived [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/rational-case-why-obama-supported-gay-marriage-did-174825772.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 13:48:25 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/rational-case-why-obama-supported-gay-marriage-did-174825772</guid></item><item><title>Pay no attention to the pollster behind the curtain</title><description>There are many ways to keep score on whether Barack Obama or Mitt Romney has better odds of winning the general election, which is almost exactly six months away. Here at The Signal, we are fervent evangelists of the political prediction markets, where people place real money on the line to bet on the winner. [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/pay-no-attention-pollster-behind-curtain-194657457.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 15:46:57 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/pay-no-attention-pollster-behind-curtain-194657457</guid></item><item><title>Is the New Jersey tunnel project too big to succeed? The economist’s view.</title><description>Anyone who commutes in to New York from New Jersey knows that the smallest glitch can throw the entire rail system into chaos, delaying 1,300 trains worth of people. Many argue that there is an urgent need for a new rail link between the two states, but viable plans to build such a thing have yet [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/jersey-tunnel-project-too-big-succeed-economist-view-154026455.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 11:40:26 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/jersey-tunnel-project-too-big-succeed-economist-view-154026455</guid></item><item><title>Hollande favored as next French President</title><description>François Hollande, the Socialist Party candidate for president of France, has an 85.3 percent likelihood of capturing the presidency from incumbent Nicolas Sarkozy in the upcoming election. At this point, the other three major competitors: Marine Le Pen (far-right), Jean-Luc Melenchon (far-left), and François Bayrou (center) have negligible likelihoods of victory. It is almost certain [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/hollande-favored-next-french-president-150709105.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 11:07:09 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/hollande-favored-next-french-president-150709105</guid></item><item><title>Romney’s top-five vice presidential nods: Who’s the potential time bomb?</title><description>Now that the race for the Republican nomination is effectively over, Mitt Romney's campaign is speaking publicly about who they might choose as his running mate. While the prediction markets we rely on for forecasting elections also take action on vice-presidential nominees, this is a different type of race, decided by a small council of insiders [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/romney-top-five-vice-presidential-nods-potential-time-195339078.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 15:53:39 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/romney-top-five-vice-presidential-nods-potential-time-195339078</guid></item><item><title>With Santorum out, it’s Ron Paul, not Newt Gingrich, who benefits (a little)</title><description>Although he had vowed to stay in the race through the Pennsylvania primary, Rick Santorum dropped out of the Republican nominating contest Tuesday, effectively clearing the way for Mitt Romney to secure the nod. While Santorum was still running, there was a lot of speculation as to whether Newt Gingrich's supporters would go to the former [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/santorum-ron-paul-not-gingrich-benefits-little-154128548.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 11:41:28 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/santorum-ron-paul-not-gingrich-benefits-little-154128548</guid></item><item><title>Should Santorum supporters in Pennsylvania vote for Romney? An economist’s advice</title><description>The future of the Republican primary hinges on Pennsylvania, where Rick Santorum must win his home state to hang on to his tenuous position in the race. The political gambling markets that we watch so closely are extremely confident that Mitt Romney will ultimately win the nomination. This gives Santorum supporters in Pennsylvania an interesting choice [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/santorum-supporters-pennsylvania-vote-romney-economist-advice-163435432.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 12:34:35 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/santorum-supporters-pennsylvania-vote-romney-economist-advice-163435432</guid></item><item><title>The Yahoo News Delegate Calculator: An interactive look at the primary odds</title><description>Rick Santorum may be pinning his last ditch hopes on the Pennsylvania primary to boost his waning campaign, but in reality it's impossible for the former Senator to catch up to Mitt Romney, given his runaway lead in the delegate count. But, that doesn't mean Santorum can't inflict another kind of damage on the former [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/yahoo-delegate-calculator-interactive-look-primary-odds-195241348.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 15:52:41 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/yahoo-delegate-calculator-interactive-look-primary-odds-195241348</guid></item><item><title>Markets: Romney will win Wisconsin and Maryland primaries</title><description>Mitt Romney's odds of winning Wisconsin, which holds its primary alongside Maryland and the District of Columbia on Tuesday, have been very good for about 10 days, according to both the political prediction markets and the major polls. We are very confident that he will win Wisconsin, where his odds currently sit at 96.2 percent. [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/markets-romney-win-wisconsin-maryland-primaries-200102624.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 16:01:02 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/markets-romney-win-wisconsin-maryland-primaries-200102624</guid></item><item><title>Markets predict Supreme Court will overturn health care law, but uncertainty is high</title><description>Today, the nine Supreme Court justices will cast preliminary votes on the fate of the Affordable Care Act. The result, which can change over the coming weeks as the justices prepare and exchange opinions and dissents, will not be announced to the public until June, but the political markets are doing business trading shares on [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/markets-predict-supreme-court-overturn-health-care-law-171930393.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 13:19:30 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/markets-predict-supreme-court-overturn-health-care-law-171930393</guid></item><item><title>Will Greece abandon the euro? Markets say yes, within 3 years.</title><description>There has been mounting speculation that Greece's economic woes will cause a breakup in the eurozone, the group of countries that share the euro as their currency. Like elections and sporting events, the online markets allow people to place bets on the likelihood that this will happen, giving us a means of predicting the odds. [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/greece-abandon-euro-markets-yes-within-three-years-181559254.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 14:15:59 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/greece-abandon-euro-markets-yes-within-three-years-181559254</guid></item><item><title>Twitter unhappy over Justice Kennedy’s outsized influence in health care arguments</title><description>As the Supreme Court concludes oral arguments on the Affordable Care Act, we're tuning our Twitter Machine to health care subjects to see what's striking a nerve in social media outlets. On Tuesday, our trend detection software turned up significant interest in Justice Anthony Kennedy, widely perceived to be the swing vote on the politically [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/twitter-unhappy-over-justice-kennedy-outsized-influence-health-175725246.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 13:57:25 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/twitter-unhappy-over-justice-kennedy-outsized-influence-health-175725246</guid></item><item><title>Election prediction scorecard: Markets got 21 of 26 forecasts correct in first half of primary</title><description>As we reach the halfway mark in primary season, the Signal is pausing to take stock of our predictions so far and how effective the political markets have been in forecasting the winner. We've made calls at least a week in advance for 26 primary contests so far—every matchup, excluding territories and nontraditional matchups in [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/election-prediction-scorecard-markets-got-21-26-forecasts-182651347.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 14:26:51 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/election-prediction-scorecard-markets-got-21-26-forecasts-182651347</guid></item><item><title>Previews: Louisiana (politics) and Kentucky (basketball)</title><description>Rick Santorum is going to win the Louisiana primary today with 97 percent certainty. Then he is highly likely to lose the three following primaries on April 3 to front-runner Mitt Romney: Washington, D.C. (Romney at 96.3 percent), Maryland (Romney at 97.1 percent), and Wisconsin (Romney at 90.6 percent). More importantly, Romney is now 91.1 [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/previews-louisiana-politics-kentucky-basketball-162215562.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 12:22:15 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/previews-louisiana-politics-kentucky-basketball-162215562</guid></item><item><title>NCAA Tournament: Kentucky still dominating odds going into Sweet Sixteen</title><description>Once again, we're taking a break from politics to discuss the most pressing upcoming contest in America: March Madness. Kentucky heads into the Sweet Sixteen in the same place it was a week ago, the overwhelming favorite to win the championship at a 29.9 percent likelihood of victory. Mitt Romney is slightly more likely to [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/ncaa-tournament-kentucky-still-dominating-odds-going-sweet-143529553.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 10:35:29 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/ncaa-tournament-kentucky-still-dominating-odds-going-sweet-143529553</guid></item><item><title>Once again, Obama crashes Republican primary Twitter party</title><description>In the days leading up to the Illinois primary, the press played up the possibility of an upset victory for Rick Santorum's campaign. But Mitt Romney had a good day on Tuesday, winning the Illinois contest by a comfortable margin. The networks' projection that Mitt Romney had won led to the highest volume spike on [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/once-again-obama-crashes-republican-primary-twitter-party-154940865.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 11:49:40 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/once-again-obama-crashes-republican-primary-twitter-party-154940865</guid></item><item><title>Romney’s odds in Illinois safe as polls open</title><description>Mitt Romney is poised to capture an easy victory tonight in the Illinois primary. The prediction markets currently give the former governor a 97.4 percent chance of winning the state, with Rick Santorum trailing at just 3.2 percent. We've seen Santorum overcome long odds before, but not at this steep of a disadvantage going into [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/romney-odds-illinois-safe-polls-open-135749500.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 09:57:49 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/romney-odds-illinois-safe-polls-open-135749500</guid></item><item><title>Political Search Trends: The partisanship behind popular Web queries</title><description>Linguistic researchers have gotten very good at teaching computers to recognize a person's political bent when he or she takes to Twitter to spout off about politics. Thanks to their algorithms, we can measure how positive or negative people are about candidates and topics on the microblogging platform without tasking some poor junior staffer with reading [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/political-search-trends-partisanship-behind-popular-queries-182344003.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 11:31:44 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/political-search-trends-partisanship-behind-popular-queries-182344003</guid></item><item><title>NCAA Predictions: Kentucky is favorite to win, East is wide open</title><description>Like the rest of the nation, we're temporarily suspending our interest in politics to devote every ounce of our mental energy to the NCAA men's basketball tournament. Fortunately, the same online betting sites we use to predict presidential elections can give us a lot of information about March Madness. Kentucky is the top ranked NCAA [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/kentucky-favorite-team-east-most-wide-open-region-151907340.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 11:19:07 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/kentucky-favorite-team-east-most-wide-open-region-151907340</guid></item><item><title>Twitter softens (slightly) on Santorum after Alabama and Mississippi wins</title><description>As voters warm to Santorum, the often-hostile ranks of Twitter also appear to be softening on the insurgent Republican candidate. A week ago, on Super Tuesday night, we saw a manifestly negative reaction to his speech, as measured by our in-house algorithms that measure sentiment in tweets. Santorum's victory speech last night registered far more [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/twitter-softens-slightly-santorum-alabama-mississippi-wins-180332862.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 14:03:32 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/twitter-softens-slightly-santorum-alabama-mississippi-wins-180332862</guid></item><item><title>Santorum’s wins knock Gingrich out of the running in Louisiana</title><description>Following last night's big wins in Alabama and Mississippi, Rick Santorum has delivered the knockout blow to Newt Gingrich that he has long desired. Gingrich may or may not actually drop out of the race in the next few days, but he is no longer a viable alternative to Santorum in the anyone-but-Romney vote. Our [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/santorum-wins-knock-gingrich-running-louisiana-152759099.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:27:59 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/santorum-wins-knock-gingrich-running-louisiana-152759099</guid></item><item><title>Santorum wins Alabama and Mississippi (and you read it here first)</title><description>10:52 p.m. We're pleased to have been the first to call Mississippi, which several major outlets now confirm. The two victories feed the narrative that Romney cannot win among traditional conservatives, but do little to change the delegate math that still favors the former governor. 10:29 p.m. ET: The Signal is tentatively calling Mississippi for [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/santorum-romney-alabama-mississippi-primary-predictions-010901509.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 21:09:01 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/santorum-romney-alabama-mississippi-primary-predictions-010901509</guid></item><item><title>Gingrich leads narrowly in Alabama and Mississippi primaries</title><description>After a Super Tuesday night that was more protracted than it was surprising, Tuesday contests in Alabama and Mississippi look like they'll be two of the more exciting primaries of the season. Our predictions, based on the political prediction markets, give a slight edge to Newt Gingrich in both states: 64.4 percent likely to win in [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/gingrich-leads-narrowly-alabama-mississippi-primaries-153540892.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 11:35:40 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/gingrich-leads-narrowly-alabama-mississippi-primaries-153540892</guid></item><item><title>The imaginary connection between tax rates and GDP</title><description>The richest Americans currently pay a 35 percent tax on income over a certain threshold. This is a divisive subject between the two major parties that is sure to come up in the general election. Both Mitt Romney and Rick Santorum propose plans that would lower the rate to 28 percent. Newt Gingrich's plan includes a flat [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/does-28-top-marginal-tax-rate-mean-175706337.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 13:57:06 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/does-28-top-marginal-tax-rate-mean-175706337</guid></item><item><title>Why we’re happy we got one prediction wrong on Super Tuesday</title><description>On Super Tuesday, the Signal got 9 out of 10 election predictions correct, following up on an Oscar night where we got 3 of 4 award picks right. Not bad, but we really wish we didn't have those two annoying blemishes, right? In fact, we're delighted! When the markets are functioning properly, we expect to [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/why-happy-got-one-prediction-wrong-super-tuesday-150945515.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 10:09:45 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/why-happy-got-one-prediction-wrong-super-tuesday-150945515</guid></item><item><title>As go the prediction markets, so goes Ohio</title><description>Ten states voted in caucuses and primaries on Super Tuesday, but you could be forgiven for thinking only Ohioans were holding a primary contest, given the news industry's relentless obsession with the state. Now that the dust has settled, let's have a look at how poll-based and market-based prediction engines fared in foreseeing the victor. [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/prediction-markets-goes-ohio-153233204.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 10:32:33 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/prediction-markets-goes-ohio-153233204</guid></item><item><title>Sarah Palin crashes Super Tuesday party on Twitter</title><description>Rick Santorum won the zero-delegate Twitter primary on Super Tuesday with the two largest spikes in mentions over the course of the night, but his closest competition wasn't fellow candidate Mitt Romney. The silver medal in the most-tweeted competition was a tie between Newt Gingrich and none other than Sarah Palin, whose CNN interview in [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/sarah-palin-crashes-super-tuesday-party-twitter-162430415.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:24:30 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/sarah-palin-crashes-super-tuesday-party-twitter-162430415</guid></item><item><title>Early Ohio returns prompted mini-panic in political prediction markets</title><description>Several very interesting things happened in the political prediction markets on Super Tuesday. As you would expect, most of them had to do with Ohio. Going into the day, we predicted that Mitt Romney would win seven states to Rick Santorum's two and Newt Gingrich's one. This was off by one: Santorum took North Dakota, [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/early-ohio-returns-prompted-mini-panic-political-prediction-150838337.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 10:08:38 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/early-ohio-returns-prompted-mini-panic-political-prediction-150838337</guid></item><item><title>Online, voters still getting to know Santorum</title><description>On Super Tuesday, Yahoo! Search trends suggested that voters are still generally less familiar with Rick Santorum than with Mitt Romney. The top searches for Santorum still dealt with fairly basic topics, like "Rick Santorum on the issues," "Rick Santorum biography," and even "how much does Rick Santorum weigh?" Nearly half of Romney's top search terms, [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/online-voters-still-getting-know-santorum-045940736.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 23:59:40 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/online-voters-still-getting-know-santorum-045940736</guid></item><item><title>After scare, Romney almost certain to win Ohio</title><description>11:14 PM ET: After a seesaw night, in which the Signal was drafting explanations for why we don't expect to get every prediction right, we're calling Ohio for Romney. The markets are now 97 percent in Romney's favor, in large part because the last 15 percent of the vote to be reported is primarily from [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/super-tuesday-expect-003136311.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 19:31:36 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/super-tuesday-expect-003136311</guid></item><item><title>Romney goes for the kill on Super Tuesday</title><description>We have held all along that Mitt Romney will be the Republican Party's nominee for president. Since his double win last week in Arizona and Michigan, his odds in the prediction markets have jumped above 80 percent. That's likely to go up again after Super Tuesday, since the most likely scenario has Romney winning 7 of [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/romney-goes-kill-super-tuesday-205640365.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 15:56:40 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/romney-goes-kill-super-tuesday-205640365</guid></item><item><title>Twitter users lobby Limbaugh advertisers to drop business (or not) over Fluke controversy</title><description>We know from studies of tweets around elections and controversies like the Susan G. Komen-Planned Parenthood dustup that Twitter imitates life. As expected, we see the same fine-tuned reactions to Rush Limbaugh's verbal assault on Sandra Fluke, the Georgetown law student who was blocked from testifying to Congress that the private Jesuit and Catholic university's [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/twitter-uses-lobby-limbaugh-advertisers-drop-business-not-152320262.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 10:23:20 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/twitter-uses-lobby-limbaugh-advertisers-drop-business-not-152320262</guid></item><item><title>Could Putin need two rounds to win the Russian presidency? Not likely.</title><description>Russians will go to the polls on Sunday to elect their next President, and as over 30,000 web pages note verbatim, Vladimir Putin is "expected to win." But just how certain is "expected" in the often-shady world of Russian politics? We're no Kremlinologists, but we can find a reliable gauge of Putin's likelihood of winning [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/could-putin-two-rounds-win-russian-presidency-not-151710421.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 10:17:10 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/could-putin-two-rounds-win-russian-presidency-not-151710421</guid></item><item><title>Romney has no chance in Massachusetts in November, contrary to what our predictions say</title><description>Two weeks ago, we unveiled our model of presidential elections based on data from the past ten election cycles, which currently predicts that President Obama has a fragile advantage over his eventual opponent. We currently project that the president will win 303 electoral votes in November. But if the economic or job approval numbers slide [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/romney-lose-massachusetts-november-why-math-wrong-171308063.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 12:13:08 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/romney-lose-massachusetts-november-why-math-wrong-171308063</guid></item><item><title>Romney’s ‘oil we deserve’ quote resonated most on Twitter</title><description>As the Michigan primary lurched to its conclusion, the Twitter wit @LOLGOP seemed to best sum up the stakes for Mitt Romney: "HEADLINE: Michigan torn over whether to bail out Mitt Romney." By the time Arizona and then Michigan went to the Romney column, our analysis of tweets around the election registered its highest overall [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/romney-oil-deserve-quote-resonated-most-twitter-143726761.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 09:37:26 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/romney-oil-deserve-quote-resonated-most-twitter-143726761</guid></item><item><title>As expected, markets congeal around Romney after big ‘enough’ victory in Michigan</title><description>Strictly by the numbers, Mitt Romney's narrow victory last night in his home state of Michigan was modest. He won only 3 percent more votes than second-place finisher Rick Santorum and, because the primary is not winner take all, the two candidates will split the real prize -- Republican delegates -- nearly equally. In his [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/expected-markets-congeal-around-romney-big-enough-victory-142319831.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 09:23:19 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/expected-markets-congeal-around-romney-big-enough-victory-142319831</guid></item><item><title>What to expect if Romney (or Santorum) wins Michigan</title><description>Update, 9:49 p.m. ET: Mitt Romney is now very likely to carry the state of Michigan. With 50% of the state reporting he is up by almost 20,000 votes to Rick Santorum and we project him as 96.9 percent likely to hold that lead to victory. The markets reacted quickly tonight allowing The Signal to [...]</description><link>http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/signal/expect-romney-santorum-wins-michigan-011057982.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 20:10:57 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">blogs/signal/expect-romney-santorum-wins-michigan-011057982</guid></item></channel>
</rss>
<!-- fe166.global.media.ch1.yahoo.com compressed/chunked Sun Jun 17 22:18:35 UTC 2012 -->
